eltima.com 2005-03-07

# Internet Privacy application, Decompiler mx SWF, Optimizer

|    
|  **Did you know?**

Eltima offers all types of information and technical support to its clients: e-mail, phone, instant messengers. Our support department is one of the best on the market. 

**Newsletter**  
  
---|---  

| 

Privacy Policy

Eltima Software GmbH respects your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to our corporate website, sites of our departments and products, you prefer to control the way you share your personal information and preferences. When you engage in activities on our website such as ordering/registering products, accessing members-only areas, requesting technical support, or subscribing to newsletters and e-mail publications, you may be asked to provide us with some identifying information. 

For processing purchases we use secure online payment systems which take great precautions to ensure that your personal information and credit card information are kept secret and used only for matters related to your order. For details we recommend that you see privacy policies of these payment systems. 

Additional information we may ask you for to be able to take part in other activities on our website or within our products may include name, mailing address, telephone number, facsimile numbers, e-mail address, and other demographic information that will enable us to better understand the requirements of our customers and to continue to provide high quality products and services. This information request will be optional and required only to engage in certain activities. By choosing to enter the requested information when prompted, you may be eligible to receive demonstration versions of new software, extended functionality, user tips and product information, newsletters and special offers. All of your private information that you provide is stored and protected by your user-established email and Password. The information you post in message boards is available to others outside of the website. Please remember that whenever you disclose personal information publicly, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Also, any information you transmit online in such forums will be made public and we cannot control nor are we responsible for the use any third parties may make of such information. 

We will guard the personal information you share with us to ensure the content, services, and advertising that we provide on eltima.com and other Eltima websites are always tailored to your current, designated preferences. You can maintain the accuracy of information provided by updating it and/or your preferences at any time. 

When you provide Eltima Software GmbH with your name (or alias), e-mail address, mailing address, or telephone number, we may use the provided information to alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information, classes, new services, and other Eltima Software GmbH related information. 

Eltima Software respects the rights users give us when choosing to receive e-mail communications and enforces internal policies to preserve those rights. It is our objective to retain the long-term ability to continue to communicate with our users. 

If you do not want Eltima Software GmbH to contact you, you may unsubscribe at any time, either online or by contacting Eltima Software GmbH directly. For instructions, please see the "Contacts" section or e-mail us at [support@eltima.com](mailto:support@eltima.com)

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still visit most of Eltima Software GmbH Web sites. However, you will not have access to areas that require personal identification. 

Eltima Software GmbH also uses web log analysis software on our server and keeps the reports for internal use; we do not use these reports to identify individual users except in cases of deliberate mis-use of our systems. We do not share our server usage logs with third parties. 

Personal information we collect is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access, and we protect this information from loss or misuse, and from unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. 

Eltima Software uses the data collected from Web site visitor user sessions in aggregate form only and does not collect any personally identifiable information. Use of this information helps us better understand what users are seeking and learning at our Web site(s) and helps us identify potential navigation issues. 

Eltima Software GmbH is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of non-Eltima Software Web sites to which this Site or any other of our web sites may link to. When you access a non-Eltima web site, you do so at your own risk. Eltima Software GmbH is not responsible for the reliability of any data, opinions, advice, or statements made on third-party sites. We provide these links merely as a convenience. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of such sites as their privacy practices may differ from ours. 

If we find it appropriate or desirable to change our privacy policy taking to consideration our users' feedback or our need, we will post changes as soon as they go into effect so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how it would be used, and under what circumstances we would disclose it. We recommend that you print a copy of this policy for your reference and revisit this policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. Your accessing our Web sites signifies your acceptance of any changes. 

If you would like to comment or have any questions concerning our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@eltima.com](mailto:support@eltima.com). 

|
